We're trying out the things I bought in Sapporo together. I don't want to see that.
I bought so many things—you have to try these right away. Erborio's CC Eye
I’ll start with the cream. This product is like an under-eye brightener
Since it contains hyaluronic acid and CC cream, it’s natural for the skin
It evens out the skin tone. The brightness it adds to the under-eye area
The photo is really beautiful. Especially when she's not wearing makeup.
that you can easily apply under your eyes
a product. Because it makes your eye area look better
It looks like it's still there—as if you'd applied something
No.
This is a product I’ll be using a lot
which is, again, the product I tried most recently.
I'm really curious to see if this color will look muddy.
It's a pretty cool-toned product—no orange in it. Oh, but look, look
I really didn’t have high hopes for this product because of its color, but it actually looks better the more you apply it.
A perfect contour shade. Oh, I love it.
And it spreads out beautifully and evenly, and
We’ve finally gotten to that product I’ve been dying to see. I’m glad I made it in time
if you’ve tried it. I’m talking about the new Stick blush. I’ve tried it myself
I picked the color; I don’t know if I did the right thing. We’ll see.
That’s exactly why I bought it. It’s so beautiful
It’s shiny. But it’s a pretty greasy product.
The color range of the blushes is so beautiful. No matter which one you choose, you’ll be amazed.
It works well with any eye makeup color.
I bought this thinking that. The product is very creamy like this
I said that because he slipped away like butter
This either removes the foundation underneath or patches it up
The patch spreads out.
Take a look at her posture. Her skin looks so...
It looks moist and shiny. That’s just how it is. And that’s how it is
I really, really liked it. The way you applied it was just like this
It looks smooth. I hope it lasts well too, because this
I absolutely love the look. I’m wondering what this Glove Face palette is
If I had waited, it wouldn’t have been in stock. I bought it while I had the chance.
I’m mixing these two colors, but you’re really going to drive me crazy.
I can't speak right now. There are some performances today that I never expected.
This is a pretty sparkly highlighter.
But there isn’t a single speck of makeup on my face right now
No. How is this possible? The authorities need to explain this. This pink one
What do you say about putting it on my eyelid? Oh, come on.
Since I finished this one, I bought a new one. This is usually
It’s marketed as a lip balm, but it’s actually one of those Korean tints you know.
It has such a beautiful color, texture, and feel
... This color, with its glass-like appearance and
It’s as light as water. I love it. We have two products from Penti.
The reflections in this lip balm
Very good.
So you can’t call this “like glass” anymore—this is glass
something beyond that. It’s as if its structure is very dense
It looks like it’s finished, but it’s definitely not. Not at all.
It doesn't smudge between the lips. And of course, the glosses don't either.
I chose the hot chocolate color.
I just love these colors.
And finally, I picked up this blush from the Sephora collection. Its balance and finish
I really liked it. Let’s try this in my next video, but let’s take a look at it first.
Oh, look at that.