[Speaker 0]: Hello, friend.
[Speaker 0]: Hello, hey there, buddy.
[Speaker 0]: Şükran, go sit next to Büşra. Okay, sir.
[Speaker 0]: What's up?
[Speaker 0]: If it’s a no, then it’s a no—even a jug of water is a no for us.
[Speaker 0]: The spout is over there, the jug is over there. It’s yours with the spout—may it bring you good fortune.
[Speaker 0]: We have nothing to do with water; it’s because of my brother.
[Speaker 0]: Are you free?
[Speaker 0]: What am I up for? Bulu Japa.
[Speaker 0]: What's up?
[Speaker 0]: Hey, neighbor? You saw us in the garden—did you think we were gardeners? I’m Mr. Özgür’s driver.
[Speaker 0]: Arif, Arif. I’m also the world flyweight boxing champion, Hatırra Baytar. He
[Speaker 0]: Heh heh. Are you doing a good job?